Thank you for watching!
Thank you for watching
Thank you for watching.
Good evening, everyone.
Good evening.
The morning chime has rung. We are CJB China.
Yes, before we start the show, we would like to choose today's MC.
We will not show everyone, this,
We don't show it.
We have the bills and we have the things,
Please vote for 1 or 2, whichever you like.
And the one with the most votes will be the MC for today's show.
So let the voting begin.
Oh no.
What should I do?
It's been so long since we've had a Kao, hasn't it? Shoals.
It's been so long.
When was the last time? It's been too long.
I wonder how long it's been.
Happy New Year?
New Year's Day? Is that the level?
That level?
Is that a lie?
You haven't been on for about a year, though. I haven't been out for about a year, though.
Has it been dawn?
Oh, it's almost time to wish you a Happy New Year.
Happy New Year.
23 years.
Please come back next year for a better year.
I will do my best.
Five, four, three, two, one, end of voting.
So, which is more?
Which is it?
Let's go for number 1 by 5, se-o-o-o, and it's me.
Yay, Mire-chan.
I'm going to do my best as MC, in place of Kao, who hasn't been here for a year.
Please do.
Yes, I'm Mirei Hoshida, the MC for today's event, and I'm the Lucky 7 of the private Ebisu study intellectual number.
And then..,
Attendance number 11, Kaho Kobayashi.
Please do me a favor.
Please do.
Let's begin.
Okay.
Let's go to the showroom of EBITCHU.
What? You haven't been here for more than a year, since September 2022.
Ah, here I am. Congratulations!
Oh, no.
Congratulations!
Wow, you haven't been here that long?
Oh, man. This is bad.
Oh no.
I'm feeling a little bit like a new member today.
Are you nervous?
Yes, I am.
You can relax.
Yes, I am. I'm nervous.
Do you want to say how you feel about today?
Well, I'll do my best.
That's someone, isn't it?
Emma Sakurai.
You know her?
The way she talks.
I knew it.
Today, I'd like to do my best with Emma.
I'll do my best.
I will do my best.
Thank you for visiting our showroom today.
What is it?
What?
Oh, please stop.
Please don't go that way.
Oh, please stop it.
Emma, we all imitate each other backstage a little bit.
Yes, yes, we do.
I've mastered it.
Yes, it's called the showroom of the 63rd Yukari de Fuu Fuu Na Showroom,
Yes. Yes.
Yes, we are the sister showroom of our sister showroom, Ukka.
It is the sister show of our sister showroom in Ukka.
Yes.
So we would like to have a spread time here.
In order for as many people as possible to see this show, I will post a picture on the official X of EBITSUYU,
I will post a picture on the official X of EBITSUYU,
Please spread the word, everyone.
Please spread the word.
What do you think?
X.
Thank you very much.
Thank you very much. Okay, everyone, please spread the word.
Please spread the word.
And today, I have an announcement.
I have an announcement.
Showroom will be celebrating its 10th anniversary this weekend, November 25th.
That's great, 10th anniversary.
That's amazing. But how many years have we been around?
EBITU TIMES, it used to be just the three of us, me, Kaho, and Ayaka.
It used to be a news program by the three of us, me, Kaho, and Ayaka.
We have been working together since September of 2005.
We have been working together for about six years now.
Thank you very much.
I'm sure you have a lot of memories, but are there any that stand out in your mind?
But, you know..,
Not yet,Still,
The three of us in EBITU TIMES are still working on it,
It goes back to the time of EBITU TIMES,
Every week, we pretend to be the newscaster and the guest,
Yoshida Lucky-kun.
Yoshida Lucky-kun was there.
The child actor's name. Actually, it's a guest who is a child actor.
I'm always the newscaster, and Ayaka is a male newscaster,
I always said that there would be a guest of some kind, and it was usually Mr. Kobayashi who would be the guest of some kind,
I think that was the hardest thing for me to face.
It's true.
Every time.
I even bought clothes for that. To prepare for the role.
Yes, that's right. And so on.
Yoshida Lucky-kun.
Oh my God, there are people who remember the kanji characters.
Really?
Isn't that amazing?
You remember.
Lucky Yoshida.
You're listening to the function of energy with ease and comfort, aren't you? Lucky.
That's right. Remember the rancher? He was a rancher.
Numa.
How old was he?
I don't know. I remember him as Numa. Numa.
Something Numa.
Numa.
Read Numa.
Read Numa. Read Numa.
He has a great sense of naming.
I was doing it.
It's terrible. But it was something like that.
I heard that everyone had their own costumes.
That's right.
That's right. We had our own costumes.
Because, you know.
I was wearing the suit I wore for my college entrance ceremony.
That's right. That's right. Me too.
You must have gone through a lot of hard work, Lucky.
He bought shirts and other things, went out to buy the missing ones, and tried to make a role for himself with them.
You did it, didn't you?
Yes, I did.
He used UNIQLO a lot.
That's right. That's right. That's right.
He was wearing a giraffe headdress and stuff.
I was there. I miss it.
It's good. I miss it.
The principal, the chief manager of the school, wanted the three of us to be able to start the season with a bang,
I told them to go for it, and they did.
I told them to do their best. Here it is, this picture.
Oh, no. Look at this.
I bought this. I went to buy it.
It's Lucky, right?
Lucky.
Oh, man.
Oh, my God. This is like a family photo.
It's funny.
Oh, no. I miss it. Oh man. I've missed it.
I missed it.
So, we did it.
But it was well-received, and it was a shrimp stew.
Yes. It was so well received that they did this for the whole group.
They decided to let us do it.
I'm very grateful.
But personally, I am very happy that everyone is using my avatar.
There are so many avatars of ordinary people.
I'm really happy about that.
When I look into the showroom, I sometimes see avatars of people who are not like me at all.
This one stands out.
So I'm glad that it's so easy to understand.
Nice designer.
Thank you very much. I thought so.
No, it's nice.
I am doing it. Keep using it.
Shrimp Bonjin.
Use it, and continue to use it, Shrimp Bonjin.
It stands out, so use it.
Please use it.
I'm also personally delivering showrooms and stuff like that.
That's right.
I have a lot of showrooms, like this Corona Disaster showroom.
I was really helped a lot.
I had a chance to talk with everyone.
That's great.
I look forward to working with you in the future.
I'm looking forward to working with you.
Yes, I will. I see that you are already working on limited avatars and gifts for the 10th anniversary in the showroom, as well as special events for the 10th anniversary, Yes, I am looking forward to seeing the showroom. We are already working on the 10th anniversary of the showroom with limited avatars, gifts, and special events for the 10th anniversary,
We would like to present a gift to all of you who have been watching our official showroom studio program, Ebichu Showroom.
Yes, we will do that.
As announced by the Showroom Official X in advance, the 10th anniversary T-shirt, which is the 10th anniversary goods of the showroom, is the one I am wearing right now.
I am wearing it.
It will be signed by both of us, plus the signatures of the next members, and the name of the winner will be written on it.
I want it.
Yes, I want it.
Please note that the name on the T-shirt will be your X account name at the time of winning.
So, I'm wearing it right now.
It's nice. I can wear it loosely.
It is one size, men's size M, and I am wearing it loosely like this.
It looks good. It seems to be resistant to sagging.
Indeed. The material is also good.
Material is good. Cute.
Cute.
The design is decorated with the usual children of this gift and others, so you showroom lovers,
I think you guys might want one.
What do you think? What do you think? What do you think?
What do you think?
Yeah, I think so. This is it.
That's it.
How is it?
It's very good.
It's important that it's not saggy.
It's all on one side.
Yes, it is.
It's pretty good.
So, please, if you go to the showroom, please wear it when you see the showroom. So by all means, showroom, if you crossed over, please wear it when you see the showroom.
Nice. Conscious.
I hope you will come out in spirit as a costume.
Yes, that's right.
Yes, I would like to wear it like this.
Like this.
How do I apply for the present campaign?
Yes.
Hashtag, showroom 10th anniversary.
And the hashtag, Epitu Showroom,
All you have to do is post on your own X.
However, if you are not a key account or not followed,
If your account is locked or you are not followed, you will not be eligible for the drawing,
Please make sure to post on a public account.
Yes, you can post on your public account.
The entry period is from now until 23:59 on Saturday, November 25.
We will announce the winners on the next distribution and send them a DM via Showroom Official X,
Yes, I'll send you a DM on the official X of the showroom after announcing the winner.
Yes, you can receive a DM from the showroom.
Don't forget to follow us on Showroom Official X so that you can receive the DMs from the showroom.
Yes.
So, please use these two hashtags to enter the contest.
Oh! I've heard that any post can be a plus, like "Epitu is cute," "Epitu is the best," or "Epitu is the only thing I bought.
It could also be something that looks cheap.
It's like, "Showroom, I'm only looking at showrooms.
Yes, that's right.
If they know that you love them, they will get to you.
Yes.
I think so.
Yes. Yes, I am.
Please get it, everyone.
Please get it.
Yes, please. So, let's get right to the planning.
Yes.
Yes, I'm going to do this today. Today's project will be like this.
We're going to call it a fun and funny survey talk.
Yay.
It's a survey talk. Survey talk.
Survey talk.
Yes. Have you ever done this?
Yes, I have.
Oh, you have.
That's surprising.
Yes, it is. That maybe.
So it's a time blouse.
I might have done it when I came here in September of that 22nd year.
Just in time.
Yes, just barely. I think it was.
So I can see it, too.
Yes.
Before a talk, a questionnaire is taken to determine the content of the talk. That is the questionnaire talk.
Yes. So, first of all, I would like to announce the theme of the talk.
Let's go ahead and do it!
The showroom was held in the first half of October, so I would like to talk about what has happened since then.
I see. Yes, that's right.
Yes, I see. The first one is Okela Disco 2023, and the second one is the New Zealand expedition, and the third one is the Kaho stage. Yes, I am. The first one is Okela Disco 2023, and the second one is the New Zealand tour, and the third one is Cajo on stage.
Yes.
I tried twice.
Wakako shines the light. And 4, Staplan Idol Fest.
Yes.
And 5, the Birthday Solo Live at Hoshinami.
Yup.
And 6, Akita Bunko.
Yes.
7. In the company.
Yeah.
8, zip line. Surprise.
Zip line.
9, Tamago. That's what it's called.
Yes.
These three. This is a little bit of this area.
Yes, it is.
This is our subject.
Yes, yes, yes.
This is basically a discussion about each event, so please take a look at the survey talk. What would you like to hear the most?
Yes, please vote.
Then, please vote. Let's start.
What do you like?
Do you care about all of this? I'm curious.
I'm a little concerned, too. Eggs.
Eggs.
I'm curious about eggs. I'm curious about eggs.
You care about eggs, don't you?
But, you know, at first. The White Hair Festival. I haven't forgotten. There was the White Feather Festival, wasn't there?
Yes, there was.
Do you want to talk about the White Feather Festival during this period?
Yes, that's right.
You participated in the Shirokou Festival at Chiayo University, didn't you?
Five, four, three, two, one.
I'll finish up.
So, first of all, which one is it?
I don't know.
Number 1?
Number 1 by far?
Okela.
Okela Disco.
Tell us about Okela Disco 2023.
Hmm?
No?
Seven?
Oh, no. Not at all.
It was a seven.
It's not one, it's seven.
Oh, no, it's true. It's a seven.
What?
Look out.
It's a seven.
Aren't these the ones that come in second or third?
I know. I'm sure you're all wondering.
I wonder what happened in the office.
Is it a story? Is it a story?
I don't recognize me, I don't remember anything.
I am.
Ah, the fight.
Yes, a fight.
What's going on, then?
Right off the bat.
I thought we were all going to be divided, but I thought we were going to start with the usual.
Yes, that's right.
We'll talk about it.
In the office.
What was that?
I was talking with a friend of mine the other day. We were talking about the distance between our destination and the city, and we decided to take a cab because it's too far to go by train.
In Tokyo, for example.
Yes, that's true.
When it is just the two of us, it is easier to split the fare, so we decided to take a cab, and we said, "Let's take a cab, let's take a cab," and then, well, there was some kind of telepathy.
I guess so.
Yes, I do.
That's for sure.
I heard a commercial of Ayumi Hamasaki saying, "She's a Pearl Tasaki, she's a Pearl Tasaki.
It is indeed playing.
This kind of thing is played all my life, so I remember it very well.
I'm sure I'll remember it.
I remember it.
And then you said, "What kind of commercials do you like?
Yeah, yeah.
And I like "GO!
Oh, I watch it.
The one with Masataka Takenouchi, who has been raised all his life, and what is he going to do? I like that kind of thing. What are you going to do now that you've been paid up for the rest of your life? What are you going to do?
Indeed.
He was talking about how he is a drunkard.
I guess so.
And then one of my friends said, "If you could participate in something like this, wouldn't you be super strong? I was like, "Sure.
That's for sure.
If I could participate in this, wouldn't I be super strong? Like that.
Yes.
Yes, for sure.
If I appear in this, won't I be super strong? Like that.
Yeah.
Sure.
Sure, yeah.
Surely, you're right.
Minami Fukuoka was famous for a long time, but now she's a teleceiver.
Indeed.
TV commercials are telecy.
Telecy.
And everyone was like, "Oh, he loves sake!
Like that.
Yeah, that's true.
That's true.
And then my friend said, "If you could participate in this kind of thing, wouldn't you be super strong?
Like, "If I could be in this kind of thing, wouldn't I be super strong?
That's true.
If I were to participate in this, I would be known to most people.
Sure.
Sure.Like, sure.
Certainly.
I wonder how I can get out of this.
I wonder if there are auditions like this?
I wonder if there is?
Nodo Sitakayo Oshizuki-san
US song N proyectoА?
Prison.
I can make another 3 songs, and I will make a lot of chicken zooms.
telefito u everyone learned it.
I'm also with A-kun, and he's helping me to wake up.
Haa....
Who is it? Who? I'm a girl friend of mine, and he's my uncle.
I have a girl friend who is an uncle.
I'm sure they're like, "Who am I? I'm like, "Who am I? He kept saying that he couldn't forget the telepathy.
Oh, I knew it. I was like, "Oh, you can't forget telepathy.
I don't know much about it, you know.
I didn't know about Minami.
I'm going to have to start speaking up, too. I'm sure you'll understand when Minami gets on board.
When Minami gets on board, I'm sure she'll understand. Like, "Oh, I see.
Oh, I see.
I see. And I knew I had to do this job for sure.
And then he asked me, like, "What do you do? And I thought, "Oh, I'm going to use this hair color to be an artist with a bit of personality,
I thought, "Oh, I'll use this hair color and say I'm an artist with a bit of personality.
Not that I am an idol.
A unique idol.
I'm an artist, so I think it's difficult. It's like, I'm going to do my best.
Oh man, I feel like a rookie. Oh man, it's a rookie feeling.
Yeah, I got through it, but then I don't know. I got through it, but then I don't know what happened.
I don't know if he thought I was a celebrity or what, but he was really nice,
And when we were about to stop at a traffic light, he turned off the meter,
He was so kind.
He said, "It's good to be here.
I guess so.
I thought, "Celebrities are very lucky.
That's what I thought. That's what I thought of Mirei.
So, for my uncle's sake, I'm going to show you this.
The commercials that play in the company.
TV commercials that run in the company.
I'm hoping to make a TV commercial for the second generation TV commercial.
We are waiting for you.
Application form.
Application form is here.
If there was an application form, we'd want it.
Like, please.
Saturday.
It's true, isn't it?
It's amazing.
Charm ghost.
But you're right, I'm curious about that commercial.
I've been listening to those commercials for a long time too.
I know what you mean. And, you know, the ones with the makeup artist.
I like it.
But not so much.
I'm a little tight on my wallet.It's a little tough on the wallet.
It's pretty expensive.
Yes, yes, yes.
But I heard that the AI judges the price and tailors it to the customer's needs.
Really?
So, for example, if you are a girl, they will give you a pearl necklace or a facial equipment.
I didn't know that. I didn't know that.
Yes, yes, yes.
I didn't know that. They use cameras to identify customers.
That's right. That's right.
That's amazing.
That's what I was talking about. Thank you very much.
I like it.
I'm going to keep working on the commercial.
I'm going to be in a commercial.
I'm going to be in commercials.
I'm going to appear in a commercial.
I will do my best.
Yes, I will.
I'll do my best.
Shall we continue?
Go on.
What would you like? What do you like?
Let's do it. Start.
What do you like? What do you like?
Oh, let's make a commercial that says, "I'm a unique artist. I am a unique artist.
Let's make it. Let's make it.
What do you think? What do you want?
Five, four, three, two, one, the end.
The end. What is it?
Two, New Zealand expedition.
Oh. Hmm?
Oh, but not yet.
Maybe our eyes are rotten today.
Maybe our eyes are bad. Our eyes are rotten today.
No, not at all. Naked eyes and contact lenses.
I'll go to an ophthalmologist tomorrow. You're right, it's 9. 9.
Nine eggs?
Who are you talking about?
Se-no, yes, it's our story.
It really happened today. It happened today. It was a shock.
First of all, we were having a lesson today.
And we were talking about this self-cooking.
And..,
I don't know,
What kind of cooking do you do? And we were like, "What kind of food do you cook for yourself?
I was like, "That's good, that's good.
I was doing it,
And then Emma..,
What? There are two kinds of eggs, right? She said, "There are two kinds of eggs, aren't there?
What do you mean?
Not the kind of eggs that are cooked that way, but the eggs as they are.
The original, the raw material. Eggs are made from eggs.
There are two kinds of ingredients, right? I mean, there are two kinds of eggs.
Two kinds? I asked,
What? Raw eggs and boiled eggs? He said, "Yes.
And I said, "Yes, raw eggs and boiled eggs, And, after all, what is a raw egg and a boiled egg?
No, you see, a boiled egg is a boiled egg because it is boiled.
What? So your mother boils them every day?
She's 16 years old, right? I was like, "Why?
Why? And Yuna asked, "She's 16, right? She asked.
Yes, that's right. And Emma thought there were two kinds of eggs, raw and boiled.
Isn't that crazy?
It's not a matter of cooking for yourself. Seriously.
It's just too funny.
It's just too much fun. I mean, normally, in the first cooking class of home economics, I would definitely, you know, make eggs. Boiled eggs.
That's right. You know, the first thing you do is boil an egg, right?
You made it, right?
That's right. And before that, we were told that we could cook an omelet, and we were going to eat boiled eggs.
Why can you cook an omelet but not a boiled egg?
That's right. That is why boiled eggs were not included in the cooking method. So, I heard that chickens are laying boiled eggs now.
What?
So, that's great. That's amazing.
It was so funny that I thought she was a little bit crazy.
I think there is something wrong with her.
I want to dig a little deeper. We are getting closer, but I still want to dig a little deeper.
Yes, that's right.
That was the egg that shocked me today.
What? What?
Yeah. You know, smoke? Smoke?
When you're filming, you use smoke to create an atmosphere.
Yeah, to create an atmosphere.
So I lied to them. I told them that if you burn a lot of smoke, people will float, and they said, "What? The sky? They floated? He was so sparkling.
When I told him it was a lie, he said, "What are you talking about?
What?
Please stop. Please don't do that!
Chochin, please don't do that!
Chochin.
Making fun of them a little is a recent hobby of mine.
It's pretty funny.
It's so funny.
I often wonder how this girl has lived all her life.
Yes, that's right.
Really?
It's too funny,
You're very good.
Pure.
It's also funny that Yuna is making fun of it.
Yuna's pretty funny, too.
Today, well, only we can see this,
Today, we worked really hard at the lesson.
She worked really hard.
We were supposed to do several songs for the college arts festival,
We choreographed about five songs in one day.
You worked really hard.
We worked really hard, and I and Hon went along as support,
By the fifth song, I was really tired,
Yuna was already wearing glasses today.
Yuna already wore glasses today,
Yes, that's right.Yes.
Glasses and bangs on the side,
But I couldn't hold my strength any longer, you know,
I was exhausted. I was exhausted,
Yes.
Yes, yes.
Yuna is like this because she is a pendulum.
Yes.
She responds very well, doesn't she?
Are you okay? He said I don't have to answer anymore.
"Do you want a boiled egg? He said.
I'm not in limbo anymore.
Yes, I am.
She was so cute.
Yes.
That's what I meant by "eggs.
Eggs are shocking, aren't they?
It was interesting.
Really, it was pretty good.
It was really interesting.
I still think it's pure.
Oh, I wonder if Yuna will fall for it.
I teased Yuna a little.
Yuna would never fall for it. She's smart.
I see.
No good.
Please let me know if you fall for it someday. Let me know if you hook up sometime.
I'll do my best.
Yes, I will. Then I would like to continue.
Continue.
Let's continue.
Next turn.
Stern.
Go ahead.
Da, da, da, chan.
That's right.
She's adorable, really.
Yes, it is. She's adorable.
Yes, it is.
How should I tease her next time?
I was just teasing you the other day,
Yeah.
I don't know..,
He said, "Try eating this gummy bear with your eyes closed.
What? What? What?
What? What? What? What's it look like? And I ate it.
And it's a really strong pungent pungent fix,
Seriously?
And it was the first shoot of the morning,
That's terrible.
I really thought it was him.
He's been beaten.
I thought it was him.
That's interesting.
Well, I'm going to make up my mind.Well, I'd like to decide all the way through.
Five, four, three, two, one, done.
We'll see this time.
Number eight.
Eight.
Why is everyone attacking from this side?
Because it's this way.
See, you're right.
We're not talking about us.
It's too soon. I'm really talking about what we just talked about.
Okay, zipline.
Okay.
This is Kaho, right?
It's really me, the other day, with my family, with my grandma and grandpa,
We went glamping with my grandma and grandpa.
Oh, my God, I love glamping.
It was also my sister's birthday, wasn't it?
Yeah, it was my sister's birthday.
And there's a YouTuber, or rather, a real-life person, that my sister likes,
I don't know if she stayed there or not, but they were announcing something like that, so it wasn't an advertisement,
She said she'd like to stay there someday, so I went there.
So I went there.
So, I went to Tanzania.
Chiba?
Yes, I went to Chiba and stayed there, and I did zip-lining for the first time.
We put on harnesses.
We went down the wire and went through the beautiful scenery.
That's the one where you go through the forest and come back?
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
That's what we did.I was jarring it.
And then, there was this, I don't know, aerial athletic activity.
We would put on wires and harnesses and go up the tree tops and clear the course by ourselves,
We did that.
What?
It looked like a lot of fun.
And it was the first time for Grandma and Grandpa to do it too.
What? Grandma and grandpa did it?
That's right.
We skied together.
Wow.
It was my sister's birthday, but Grandma and Grandpa were more excited than she was.
It was my sister's birthday, but my grandma and grandpa were more excited than she was. I recommend it.
Oh, I like it.
I was in a great mood.
It was a lot of fun.
We stayed in a log cabin and prepared a barbecue, and it was really refreshing.
It really was.
The food was delicious.
Everything is prepared for glamping, right?
That's right.
You just bring what you want to eat with you,
Heh.
I took it, but yes. I was really enjoying myself.
That's amazing. How are your legs and back doing? I'm getting questions like, "How are your legs and feet?
That's right.
Yes, I do. Isn't it amazing?
You're so energetic.
She kept saying she was scared.
I've been saying I'm scared, but I can let go of his hand because he's wearing the harness. I kept saying I was scared, but I could let go of his hand because he had that harness on.
I was already peace the moment I got off and started sliding.
I can imagine what it was like.
Yes, I can imagine.
Kaho's grandparents sometimes came to live concerts,
When they stop by Dankozaka on their way home from a family reunion or something, they get to know each other,
So, when we stop by Dankozaka or other places on our way home from a famie or something, our families get to know each other.
And then, "Oh, thanks for your hard work, Hoshino. Hoshino.
Yes, Hoshino.
Grandpa calls Mirei-chan "Hoshino.
Hoshino.
He calls Ayaka-chan and Riko-chan "chan," but Hoshino "hoshino.
Why?
Like he's my junior.
You're a mayamason, Hoshino.
Hoshino.
Why?
Yes, he was a very energetic grandma and grandpa, wasn't he?
He was a grandma and grandpa. It was a heartwarming story.
It was great.
Yes, we were kind of joking around with them, and they were walking in the air, or what do you call it, some kind of step?
Like walking in the air.
Yes, yes, yes.
Aerial walk.
There's some kind of walk thing that's going around the world.
Like that.
Like this, right? Like this, right?
Yes, like this in the air.
You see it all over TikTok, don't you?
That's right. My sister and her brother were doing it.
I don't know if they could do it, but when they were doing it, Grandpa said, "Oh, look at my regular skipping, too.
Grandpa is 80 years old, but he was skipping, just skipping.
He was a little bit...well, a little bit.
Yes, that's right. The Kobayashi character is quite unique.
The bunch is gone.
It's so spacious, isn't it? Hammock area. Hammock area. There weren't that many people there, but they were lying on the hammocks, playing enka on YouTube and singing "ahhhhh.
I was young, you know, playing YouTube and other things.
I told them to stop it. You are not giving a recital. Don't do that.
Grandma and grandpa are so young.
That's right. That's right.
The Kobayashi family is unique.
Yes, they are.
But it was fun.
It was fun.
A nice holiday.
But, you know, I want you to go there when you feel refreshed.
It's refreshing, isn't it?
It was fun. That's what I was talking about.
It's a good story. Let's continue.
Let's continue.
Boom.
Please continue.
Please.
How's it going?
I want to go camping. I want to go camping.
No, it would be fun if we all went together.
It would definitely be fun.
Yes, it would. Powerful grandpa.
You're too powerful grandpa.
Yes, he is. He's so energetic.
He said, "I want to have a drink,
I said, "That's fine, let's have a drink,
He said, "This is good," and we made a toast,
But after I took a sip, I realized he didn't want to drink much.
Because my mood changed too much.
Because it's not the same.
Five, four, three, two, one, closed.
That's it.
What's that?
Six?
Oh, you're talking about the North Bunko.
It's about the North Bunko.
Yes, the North Bunko last week?
Has it been that long already?
Last week? Last week?
Last Saturday?
Oh, it was Saturday, wasn't it?
This year, too.
Thank you very much for holding this event for the 8th time.
Thank you very much.
Today was the first time for all the members of Team Orca to come,
We also had a great turnout from Orca, Tohoku, and our staff members,
We also had the usual Akita residents who are active in the Akita area.
Yes, that's right.That's right.
There were quite a few collaborations this year.
Yes, indeed.
I think that was the most important one,
The length of the concert was very large,
I used to do the opening address and so on.
Yeah, yeah.
We're going to cut that out a little bit.
If we didn't have the time, we would have lost it.
We were doing a lot of things to make the content as rich as possible.
Yes, she wasn't here.
Yes, she had plans.
She went to protect the earth, or rather, Akita.
She had plans.
It was a little bit bad.
Yes, I wanted to use the Curitan Sword, too.
That's right.
But, you know, Akita's mood was important to me.
I was like, "I'm sorry.
Yes, yes, yes.
That's right.
Did you get the ornament?
Yes!
The day before the rehearsal, when Miyuki came on stage,
Miyuki was holding a very big one,
So, I recognized Miyuki, right?
Yeah.
Then, Miyuki, this.
You know, the one you mentioned last year. I'll give it to you.
Amazing, isn't it? It's amazing, isn't it?
What? I was like, "What?
What? I wore a pink ornament last year.
It's so cute.
I was saying how cute Miyuki was, and she really gave it to me.
You know.
No way.
What is it, a kimono?
I received an ornament.
And they said I only wore it once or twice.
What? Something you've only worn once or twice,
Is it OK? I was like, "Is it OK?
Of course it was.
I was surprised.
It wasn't like I was saying, "You can have it.
That's right. That's amazing.
So, someday,
I'll have Miyuki dress me,
That's nice.
I want to wear it together.
On the other hand, I would like to bring it to Akita Bunko next year.
That's for sure. Wouldn't that be nice?
Yes, it's amazing, isn't it?
And Miyuki was amazing.
She was too much like Akita's mother.
You know, a mother.
She brings us a lot of handmade things.
She made them.
She told us to eat them, and they were delicious.
That's right. Pickled cucumbers, for example, So. Like cucumber pickles,
We have cucumber pickles,
Pickles, pickles, pickles,
There was also something that looked like fish, right?
Yes, there were.
Is there such a thing? I thought.
Yes, there is. But it's really something,
You know, once a year,
I'm allowed to do it once a year,
I always go home with a smile on my face.
I understand.
I bought rice,
I bought some rice.
Akihabara?
Akita Furumachi. Just in time,
It was popular, you know,
I had a little bit of rice on me,
I decided to get something else.
Miyuki gave me that too.
I bought new rice in Akita Furumachi,
It's nice. It's the season.
That's right.
It's the first time I bought rice.
Akita Furumachi is delicious, isn't it?
I've never brought it home before,
I thought it was a little heavy to bring it home,
But this year,
This is the first year I'm buying rice to take home.
Did you try it? It's delicious.
I ate it. Cooked it already.I ate it. Cooked it already.
I bought Kiritanpo soup as usual.
It's instant.
You just pour in hot water and make a cup of kiritanpo soup,
It's really delicious.
It was delicious.
How was it?
It was the first time I had dinner with Tohoku-san and Orca,
We had dinner together for the first time.
After the concert. It was the first time, wasn't it?
It was the first time to eat together. I met Chai-chan, but..,
During rehearsal, but..,
We didn't have a chance to eat together for such a long time,
That's why.
We talked a lot about each other's group.
The rice shochu from Akita was delicious.
I never drank rice shochu.
I never drank it.
That's exactly what our collaboration sake was,
Because there was our collaboration sake,
Marusan's collaboration.
That too,
We can compare the sake,
We were able to compare the sake,
We could compare the drinks,
I was like, "What's going on?
I heard that he became a good drinker.
I didn't think that Tohoku-san's children could drink alcohol,
That's right. That's right.
It's shocking, isn't it?
It was originally a radio project,
I don't know,
Riko and Tohoku San-chan,
Hikaru-chan,
Hikaru wanted to have dinner together,
So we decided to have dinner together,
So, it's like...,
I see,
Hikaru-chan is like that,
And, you know..,
I was originally thinking of going home for the day,
Yuna-chan,
I'll definitely stay.
It's so crazy,
I was going to stay at Triangle Planet,
I said, "Okay, I'm leaving now. I'm leaving now,
I said, "I'm not leaving now,
I said it right then and there.
Well, it turned out that way.
Everyone in Tohoku-san is quite willing to talk to me,
I am glad to hear that.
I had never had this opportunity before, so it was a lot of fun.
Thank you very much.
Now let's continue.
This way.
Let's start!
What would you like? What would you like?
A girl I've known since I was a little girl... I'm deeply moved.
I'm sure. They've become really nice older women.
They all started wearing makeup, and they were cute to begin with,
But now they're all so much prettier.
Isn't Rine amazing?
What kind of beauty is she?
Five, four, three, two, one, done!
I'm so excited.
What do you like?
Three!
Oh, here it comes.
The stupid son of a bitch shines.
This is Mr. Kobayashi, isn't it?
I performed in a play called "An Important Story" in January,
Kei Kato, who was with me at that time, is the organizer.
I was in a play called "Important Story" in January,
I was a daily guest on the stage organized by Kei Kato, who I worked with at that time,
It was the first time for me to perform as a daily guest on the stage,
I'm sure.
And I didn't have any rehearsal,
I didn't have any rehearsals. You had one day of rehearsal, right?
Yes, one day, and it was only a few hours.
Wow.
I had already decided where I was going to perform,
Even so, there were a lot of people I had never met before,
I was really nervous.
What kind of role did you play in "River"?
Well, the main character.
I played the main character, Nokko-chan, in her childhood,This Nokko-chan, this childhood role,
She's born as a baby,
From a baby,
I'm OK if you do it as a baby,
But if you do it as a baby, it's OK, but if you do it as a baby, it's OK, but if you do it as a baby, it's OK,
And Nokko-chan, well, you know..,
It's like the world of Princess Kaguyahime.
I'm like, you know, the world of Princess Kaguyahime.
And I also played the role of the man who asks Nocco to marry him.
You played a man too?
Yes, I played the role of a man, too.
Oh, wow.
So it's great, really, it's something,
It's amazing.
It's a great variety.
Yes, I really, really, I don't know, I felt like I saw something amazing,
It's really spectacular. But it was really interesting,
Mr. K told me to really enjoy it,
I don't know...the stage actors seemed to be really enjoying themselves,
I don't know.
I mean, when I saw them doing what they love, I thought, "This is a great scene,
It's a great place to work.
Yes, it makes me very happy,
I was kind of nervous, but I had a good time.
I was kind of nervous, but it was a lot of fun.
Yes, it was.
But was it hard for you to do it at the university?
Yeah, but, you know, it was like, "I'm fine with it,
What was your account like?
Well, I had just come to the audition, and they told me to do it, I, um, I just came to the audition and you said I should do it,
I said, "I'm Kaho Kobayashi, and I'd like to audition for the role of Nocco-san's husband,
I said, "No, it's not an audition," and so on,
No, it wasn't an audition.
No, it wasn't an audition,
I don't know, it wasn't a mono-boke.
I mean, it wasn't a monoboke, but I did a little bit of mimicry,
I don't know, it wasn't a monoboke, but it was like an impersonation.
So there are parts that are very contrived or contrived.
Yes, it was a comedy. That's right. I was allowed to participate in that kind of thing.
But, I was in trouble.
Yeah.
The first day was Yashima-san.
I have the same role as Yashima-san.
What?
Oh, my God,
What kind of casting?
The bar has been raised ridiculously high.
Yes, they have.
Wow, well, it's true that later on, you will be among the great, you know, among the great people,
Yeah.
But it was like the day after Yashima-san.
The day after Yashima-san, Kaho Kobayashi.
It was terrible.
It was amazing.
And I was performing in the two-stage, so I was really nervous.
I think the people who came to the show were probably nervous too.
Oh, sure. But the hurdle is as high as Everest.
It's not good, is it? It's bad, isn't it?
It's a big name.
Yes, it is.
But it means they're expecting a lot from you, right?
I appreciate it.
No, no, no.
But really, yes, thank you, Kei.
Thank you for just one day.
Thank you very much.
Really, it was a great experience for me.
Well, let's go to the last... It's time for the ending.
Ah.
Oh, then it's the end.
The end.
Wow, a relaxed delivery today.
I was thinking, I haven't shown you the T-shirt I signed.
Oh, yeah.
Here it is.
Choo-choo.
Choo-choo-choo. Here it is.
Here we go.
Can you see it?
This plus the next one.
The members.
Yes. It's also signed by the members.
Yes.
By Athena.
Yes. Hashtag, is it the 10th anniversary of the showroom?
Showroom.
Yes. Yes.
Oh, and please, everyone, please post on X with the hashtag showrooms and the hashtag showrooms 10th anniversary.
Please do.
So, it all happened so fast, didn't it?
So fast. It all happened so fast.
Today, you worked with Kaho for a long time.
That's right.
We had dinner together just now.
We ate.
Today, you came to the showroom.
That's right.
We've been talking.
Talking.
We've been talking all day. How was it?
How was it? How was it?
Do you want to have a review meeting? He said.
A review meeting?
I don't think so.
No, I don't think so.
Not today.
How was today?
Was there anything to reflect on today?
Today, it was just the two of us, and I was kind of nervous, but it was fun.
Well, you did a good job, Ma-chan.
Today.
There are two kinds of eggs.
Maybe, but you learned two kinds today, didn't you?
Yes, I did. Yes, I learned.
Hey, Ma-chan, let's make an announcement then.
Yes, please take a look at this.
Rock, paper, scissors.
Ta-da!
Yes, this is it. I'll do it with Kobayashi or Hoto from here.
Yes.
By now, I'm sure you all know what I mean.
It's a lot of work.
It's already amazing.
On Saturday, January 6 and Sunday, January 7, 2024, at Pialina MM,
ABC University New Year's University Performing Arts Festival 2024, "Flying Dragons and Beyond," right?
Yes.
Yes, there will be a live performance.
It's a New Year's University Performance.
Well, yes, really, preparations are already underway, and there are many unexpected songs.
No, really.
I have an image of it.
I was like, "Oh, we're going to do this.
It had been so long since we had performed that we had to check the choreography of some of the songs by watching various videos.
It was like, "Oh, I missed those songs.
Yes, but I'm sure there are many songs that you like,
I think so.
I hope you will come and enjoy the show.
Please do. And Riko and I are the oldest girls,
That's right.
Please do.
I'm a woman who stands up.
I'm a woman who stands up, so I'm probably a dragon. I'm a woman who stands up, so I'm probably a dragon.
Because of course there are people who say they are going to be dragons.
I might be a dragon, or I might be flying in the sky,
We are looking forward to seeing you all.
I might be in a Jiply.
Maybe they'll be in the air. Let's have fun together. We're looking forward to seeing you.
We are looking forward to seeing you.
So let's see the final ranking.
Fifth place, thank you very much, Mayu.
Thank you very much.
And in 4th place, thank you, Nacchan from Ordinary People.
And 3rd place, thank you, Macha-san.
And 2nd place, thank you 4chan movie.
And 1st place, thank you very much, Penrabunbun.
That concludes the 63rd edition.
We will let you know about the next installment as soon as it is decided, so please look forward to it.
Is there a little more?
There will be a little more.
Really?
A few more episodes?
There's a big actress in it.
A great actress?
Is she an actress?
Are you an actress?
In the Actress Times.
I don't remember her at all.
Akiko.
That's great.
You remember so well. You remember it soooo well.
My last name was, in case you were wondering, I named her.
I was wearing a hat like an actress's hat.
But I remember the lines. I dragged it out for a while and told my family that I got it,
I said, "Tobeperion," which is a very definite line.
I don't remember it at all.
And I was smugly saying to my mom, "I took it today. I took it today, Mom.
What?
That's what I remember.
But you have a pretty good memory, you know.
Akiko, but what was it?
Akiko, what Akiko was it?
I wonder what Akiko was.
Do any of you remember it?
I wonder if there is.
I wonder.
Is there anyone?
Tobepelion.
Yes, I already told my mom and my brother.
What's going on?
He took the test today.
Kaho, why did you take it today?
Today, you took the test at the showroom.
What?
I said "tobeperion" and he got it.
What did you mean by that? Tobeperion.
What? I said, "What do you mean, 'beperion'?
That's right.
It's Akiko Hoshi.Akiko Hoshi.
Akiko Hoshi.
No, it's not.
It's Akiko Hoshi.
Me?
That's it.
That's it. Sunglasses.
Saijo, yes, Akiko Saijo.
I'm surprised you remember me.
Isn't it amazing, like a showroom?
I'm not sure if I'd call this a mania or an Ebichio showroom mania.
I want to give this T-shirt to this guy.
Isn't it nice?
Akiko Saijo will give it to the winner.
Sure thing.
Numachi is not bad either.
The songstress.
Ah, yes. Uta no Oisama is...
What?
The songstress.
Again?
What sister?
What?
Yamato.
Oh, no. I don't remember at all.
Yamafuji.
Sounds like the sister of Uta, the girl whose name is below.
Utako?
Not Utako?
Close, close, close. Close close close.
Close. What's this way?
Yamato.
Wisteria.
Mountain wisteria.
Yamafuji.
Uta's sister.
Ha-ha-ha.
The setting. Too childish.
Yamafuji, you seem to have this kind of person in your life.
Yamafuji, Kyoko?
Kyoko? Kyoko's sister?
Isn't she amazing? This showroom guy is taking notes? A lifetime.
I wonder how long it's been? Ebichio mania, showroom mania.
Isn't that great?
I want you to call yourself that.
I'm Ebichio Showroom Mania.
That's great.
Oh, that's right. I went there with my sister Kyoko.
Kyoko-sis.
Eh, this is always, you know, the face, I had decided on the name.
Yes, I talked it over with my mother.
My mother is very outgoing, you know.
I mean, she is very strict about laughter and comedy.
That's right.Right.
It's like, no, it's like, no, it's like, let's go with this.
I get it.
I've been saying that for a while.
Yes. And you told Mr. Fujii and others?
Yes.
Ask him something.
Even you, Mr. Fujii, came to the site every time.
Yes, I was nervous.
The showroom was a mess. It's like a tea party now, but the showroom was always too important.
That's right.
You were really reflecting on the situation, weren't you?
Every time.
Yes, that's right.
Mr. Fujii used to come here often with his avatar.
What? Really?
Wow.
I see.
Well, that makes me happy.
I see, you were right about the vending machine, weren't you? After we finished in the conference room.
I was thinking, "I think it would have been better to close the meeting like this.
Like, I should have said something.
But I think now is the best time to show the looseness and the members' feeling of being off.
Thank you very much for accepting that.
Thank you very much.
I appreciate it.
The times have changed.
The times have changed, too.
But I'd like to do it again, you know, out of some kind of project.But I'd like to do it again, you know, out of the project.
We used to do it with all six of us, didn't we?
What do you think? How about you and your sister members take over the project?
You want to let the younger sisters take over?
No, that sounds great.
They are Yoshida Lucky.
I'd like to play the role of Yoshida Lucky.
It's a bit of a project.
I'm sure it would be fun to do something like that.
It would be fun to do something like that.
No, no, really.
Thank you so much for everything.
Thank you very much.
Once again, congratulations to SHOWROOM on their 10th anniversary.
Congratulations.
We will continue to do a lot of EBITCHU and SHOWROOM broadcasts in the future, so please watch for the next one.
We will let you know when we decide on the next show, so please watch for the next one.
That's all for now.
That's all for us.
Bye bye.
Good night.
Thank you for watching.